[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "moduleId": 1,
    "question": "Factor: 5x2 – 15x – 20.",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "5(x-4)(x+1)"
      },
      {
        "2": "-2(x-4)(x+5)"
      },
      {
        "3": "-5(x+4)(x-1)"
      },
      {
        "4": "5(x+4)(x+1)"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "5(x-4)(x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "moduleId": 1,
    "question": "Multiply: (x – 4)(x + 5)",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "x2 + 5x - 20"
      },
      {
        "2": "x2 - 4x - 20"
      },
      {
        "3": "x2 - x - 20"
      },
      {
        "4": "x2 + x - 20"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "x2 + x - 20"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "moduleId": 1,
    "question": "Which is greater than 4?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": 5
      },
      {
        "2": -5
      },
      {
        "3": "-1/2"
      },
      {
        "4": -25
      }
    ],
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "moduleId": 1,
    "question": "Which is the smallest?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": -1
      },
      {
        "2": "-1/2"
      },
      {
        "3": 0
      },
      {
        "4": 3
      }
    ],
    "answer": -1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "moduleId": 1,
    "question": "Combine terms: 12a + 26b -4b – 16a.",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "4a + 22b"
      },
      {
        "2": "-28a + 30b"
      },
      {
        "3": "-4a + 22b"
      },
      {
        "4": "28a + 30b"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "-4a + 22b"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "moduleId": 1,
    "question": "What is 121 times 11?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": 1331
      },
      {
        "2": 1313
      },
      {
        "3": 1133
      },
      {
        "4": 3131
      }
    ],
    "answer": 1331
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "moduleId": 1,
    "question": "10001 – 101 = ?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": 1001
      },
      {
        "2": 990
      },
      {
        "3": 9990
      },
      {
        "4": 9900
      }
    ],
    "answer": 9900
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "moduleId": 1,
    "question": "What is the opposite of 6?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": 6
      },
      {
        "2": 5
      },
      {
        "3": 4
      },
      {
        "4": -6
      }
    ],
    "answer": -6
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "moduleId": 1,
    "question": "Which number has the greatest absolute value?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": 0
      },
      {
        "2": -20
      },
      {
        "3": -10
      },
      {
        "4": 10
      }
    ],
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "moduleId": 1,
    "question": "Find the sum; –1.54 + 5.093.",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": 3.553
      },
      {
        "2": 6.63
      },
      {
        "3": 3.553
      },
      {
        "4": "–6.63"
      }
    ],
    "answer": 3.553
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "moduleId": 1,
    "question": "What is the value of a^0?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "a"
      },
      {
        "2": -1
      },
      {
        "3": 0
      },
      {
        "4": 1
      }
    ],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "moduleId": 1,
    "question": "Which of these following set of numbers are factors of 24?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "2, 3, 4, 6, 8"
      },
      {
        "2": "1, 5, 12, 18"
      },
      {
        "3": "4, 7, 24"
      },
      {
        "4": "3, 9, 12"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "2, 3, 4, 6, 8"
  }
]